Preliminary Guide to the Charles Reinhart Management, Inc. Records, 1956-1992
American Dance Festival Archives
- Subject Files, 1956-1992
  - Mini-Panel, Feb. 9, 1977 (Box 37)
  - Mini-Panel Meeting II for 1978-1979 Directory, June 6-7, 1977 (Box 37)
  - Rejectee Complaints, 1978-1979 Directory, Responses (Box 37)
  - Dance Advisory Panel, Review Panel Recommendations for 1978-1979 Directory (Box 37)
  - Letters to Applicants from NEA for 1978-1979 Directory (Box 37)
  - Letters of Acceptance/Rejection to DMS/Dance Co., 1978-1979 (Box 37)
  - Letters of Acceptance/Rejection to DMS/Dance Co., 1978-1979 (Box 37)
  - DMS Applicants: Reviewed, Accepted (or both), 1978-1979 (Box 38)
  - Mini-Panel Meeting, Results, Aug. 1, 1975 (Box 38)
  - AIS/DC Company Applicants Master File, 1976-1977 (Box 38)
  - Dance Component Applicants, Releases, NEA Corres., 1976-1977 (Box 38)
  - Review Process Consultant Availability, 1976-1977 (Box 38)
  - Interested Dance Movement Teachers and Cos. Not on Program, 1976-1977 (Box 38)
  - Consultant Reports (Box 38)
  - DMS and Cos. Who Wish To Reapply to AIS/DC, 1976-1977 (Box 38)
  - AIS/DC Applicants (Expressing Interest), 1977-1978 (Box 38)
  - Americana Dance Theatre, Applied 1974 (Box 38)
  - Arlington Dance Theatre, Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - Bhaskar Dances of India, Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - Boston Ballet, Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - Chicago Dance Troupe, Withdrawn, Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - First Chamber Dance Company, Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - Ballet Denver, Applied 1974 (Box 38)
  - 5x2 Dance Company, Applied 1974 (Box 38)
  - Fusion, Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - Lotte Goslar's Pantomime Circus, Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - Guthrie-Rotante DC, Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - Bert Houle and Sopie Wibaux, Applied 1974 (Box 38)
  - Bruce King Dance Concert, Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - Maryland Dance Theatre, Withdrawn, Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - The Moving Co. Applied 1974 (Box 38)
  - Walter Nicks Dance Theatre, Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - Valentina Ouhansky D.D.E Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - San Francisco Ballet, Withdrawn, Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - Edith Stephan Dance Co., Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - Tokunaga Dance Ko., Applied Fall 1974 (Box 38)
  - Chemical Bank (Box 38)
  - Correspondence: Lee Lichter, 1985-1987 (Box 38)
  - ADF Pension Correspondence, Employer Designed (Mazzola) (Box 38)
  - CRMI Tax Info, 1988 (Box 38)
  - CRMI Taxes, 1992 (Box 38)
  - CRMI Tax Info, 1990 (Box 38)
  - Tucker Anthony and R.L. Day, Inc. (Box 38)
  - CRMI Pension 1988, Tucker, Anthony, Acct. #015-07268, ID #13-2557611 (Box 38)
  - CRMI 1988, Tucker, Anthony, Acct. #015-07268, ID #13-2557611 (Box 38)
  - CRMI Pension Trust Correspondence (Box 38)
  - CRMI Pension Trust Correspondence (Box 38)
  - CRMI Profit Sharing 1988, Tucker, Anth., Acct. #015-07269, I.D. #13-2557611 (Box 39)
  - CRMI Bank Statements and Info (Box 39)
  - CRMI:Profit-Sharing Correspondence (Box 39)
  - CR, IRA-R, Tucker Anthony, Acct: 019-47852 (Box 39)
  - CR IRA Correspondence (Box 39)
  - Tucker Anthony: General (Box 39)
  - H: Harris Communications (Box 39)
  - Audit on Contracts, C22, C42, expenses, 1971-1973 (Box 39)
  - Chronological Correspondence NEA Contracts, 1971-1978 (Box 39)
  - Contract NEA C 22, 1971-1972 (Box 39)
  - Solicitation and Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 39)
  - Budget and Solicitation, 1972-1973 (Box 39)
  - Voucher, Accounting Sheets, 1971-1972 (Box 39)
  - Contract NEA C42 and Amendment, 1972-1973 (Box 39)
  - NEA C53 (DTP) and Amendment, C56 (AIS) and Amendment, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
  - Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
  - Voucher, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
  - Budget, Contract, 1974-1975 (Box 39)
  - Voucher's Contract, 1974-1975 (Box 39)
  - Contract C90, AIS/DTP plus Amendment, 1974-1975 (Box 39)
  - NEA Voucher (C-116-A), 1975-1976 (Box 39)
  - Contract, NEA C 116, 1975-1976 (Box 39)
  - Contract AIS, 1975-1976 (Box 39)
  - AIS Contract, NEA C 160, 1976-1977 (Box 39)
  - AIS Contract, Negotiated Contract, C 160, 1976-1977 (Box 39)
  - DTP Contract, NEA C 161, 1976-1977 (Box 39)
  - Contract, Budget Specifications, 1976-1977 (Box 39)
  - AIS Contract Solicitation, 1976-1977 (Box 39)
  - AIS Solicitation and Contract, PC 77-11, 1977-1978 (Box 39)
  - NEA Contract Guidelines for AIS/DC, 1977-1978 (Box 39)
  - AIS Contract, Revised Budget/Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 39)
  - AIS Contract Amendment, 1977-1978 (Box 39)
  - AIS Contract Correspondence/Notes, 1977-1978 (Box 39)
  - NEA Internship Program (Box 39)
  - DTP Program Solicitation, 1977-1978 (Box 39)
  - DTP Contract, Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 39)
  - AIS, England, 1979 (Box 39)
  - NEA-PC-77-11($130, 200, amended), AIS Contract, 1977-1978 (Box 39)
  - NEA-C-77-10($50, 450) DTP Contract, 1977-1978 (Box 39)
  - Audit, NEA, A-77-146 (Box 39)
  - NEA Contracts with CRMI, Final Reports/Govt. Release Form (Box 39)
  - Audit (Box 39)
  - Audit (Box 39)
  - National Endowment For The Arts, Artists-in-Schools Program/Dance Component, Directory of Dance Companies and Dance Movement Specialists, 1980-1981 (Box 40)
  - Monk (Box 40)
  - Monk (Box 40)
  - Monk, Juice, Program (Box 40)
  - Europe, 1969 (Box 40)
  - Don Redlich (Box 40)
  - AIS Dance Component, Directory Listing and Number of Residencies Log, 1980-1981 (Box 40)
  - AIS Calendars, 1979-1980 (Box 40)
  - History of the AIS Review Process (Box 40)
  - AIS Statistics, 1981-1982 (Box 40)
  - Statistical Information, Artists-in-Schools/Dance Component, 1970-1976 (Box 40)
  - Statistics for Joe (Box 40)
  - AIS/Dance Component, Statistical Information on SAAs and Artists, 1980-1981 (Box 40)
  - AIS Statistics, 1970-1979 (Box 40)
  - AIS Statistics, 1979-1980 (Box 40)
  - AIS, 1978-1979 (Box 40)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, General and with DMS and DC, 1979 (Box 40)
  - Memos to DMS and DC, 1978-1979 (Box 40)
  - DMS Payment Poll, D.Co., 10% Variance Poll (Box 40)
  - AIS Sampler Program Information, 1979-1981 (Box 40)
  - David Doherty Visa Material (Box 40)
  - Work On One (Box 40)
  - Opera New England Of Maine, Inc., 1975 (Box 40)
  - Fairfield (Box 40)
  - Opera New England, 1974-1975 (Box 40)
  - Northeastern Connecticut (Box 40)
  - Northeastern Connecticut, Finis (Box 40)
  - Northeastern Connecticut (to be typed for write up) (Box 40)
  - Northeastern Connecticut (to be typed for write up) (Box 40)
  - Worcester (Box 41)
  - Original Interviews (Box 41)
  - New Mexico SAC Grant Letters, 1973-1974 (Box 41)
  - Louise Tate Correspondence, 1975 (Box 41)
  - Opera New England, 1974-1975 (Box 41)
  - Evaluation Forms (Box 41)
  - Opera Worcester, Inc., 1975 (Box 41)
  - Project Management, Opera New England, Informational Packet, 1974 (Box 41)
  - Contracts (Box 41)
  - New Hampshire, 1974-1975 (Box 41)
  - Interviews (Box 41)
  - Opera New England, 1974 (Box 41)
  - Opera New England (Box 41)
  - Europe (Box 41)
  - Music (Box 41)
  - Reviews (Box 41)
  - The Glen Tetley Dance Company, 1969 (Box 41)
  - Tetley, Technical (Box 41)
  - Fire Island (Box 41)
  - Aptitudes and Miscellaneous (Box 41)
  - Correspondence (Box 41)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 41)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 41)
  - Phakavali, 1962 (Box 42)
  - Review Excerpts (Box 42)
  - Old Booking Letters (Box 42)
  - Les Grands Ballets Canadiens (Box 42)
  - Les Grands Ballets Canadiens (Box 42)
  - Capezio Award (Box 42)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Co., Mutual Payroll Book, 1966 (Box 42)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Co., Mutual Payroll Book, 1964-1965 (Box 42)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Co., Mutual Payroll Book, 1968-1969 (Box 42)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Co., Mutual Payroll Book, 1967-1968 (Box 42)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Co., Mutual Payroll Book, 1968-1969 (Box 42)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Co., Mutual Payroll Book, 1970 (Box 42)
  - Paul Taylor, Unemployment, Mar. 1970 (Box 42)
  - Paul Taylor Taxes, 1970 (Box 42)
  - Paul Taylor, State Fund (Box 42)
  - Europe, 1968 (Box 42)
  - Paul Taylor, Payroll (Box 42)
  - Cliff Keuter, 1967-1968 (Box 42)
  - Jane Kosminsky, Karen Levey, Molly Susan Reinhart, Compensation, 1965-1967 (Box 42)
  - Paul Taylor, South America (Box 42)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, Mid-Western Performances, Mexico, 1963 (Box 42)
  - Bios, Press Reviews, Technical (Box 42)
  - Correspondence (Box 42)
  - Current Reviews (Box 42)
  - Europe (Box 42)
  - Europe (Box 42)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, Correspondence, Contracts, Itineraries, 1970-1971 (Box 43)
  - Vancouver International Festival, 1965 (Box 43)
  - Three Penny Publicity (Box 43)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, Correspondence, Contracts, Itineraries, 1970-1971 (Box 43)
  - Alba, Reyes (Box 43)
  - Alba, Reyes, Payroll (Box 43)
  - Donald McKayle, Connecticut (C.R.T.D.C.), 1969 (Box 43)
  - Alba, Reyes, Programs (Box 43)
  - Alba, Reyes, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 43)
  - Alba, 1966-1967 (Box 43)
  - Alba, Reyes, Correspondence (Box 43)
  - Three Penny Opera (Box 43)
  - Three Penny Opera (Box 43)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 43)
  - Ailey Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Ailey Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
  - Dance Repertory Co., Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - American Dance Repertory Co. Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
  - Ballet West Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Boston Ballet Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - J. Cunningham (Box 43)
  - Cunningham Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
  - Cunningham M, Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
  - Dance Theater of Harlem Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Dance Theater of Harlem Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
  - Dances We Dance Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Dances We Dance Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
  - S.F. Dancers Workshop Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
  - Dance Theater Workshop Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Dance Theater Workshop Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
  - Dehn Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Egelevesky Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Louis Falco Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Viola Farber Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - First Chamber Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - P.N.B.A., First Chamber Dispute (Box 43)
  - First Chamber Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
  - M. Graham Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - L. Goslar Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Jose Greco Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Erick Hawkins Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Hawkins Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
  - Hoving Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
  - Matteo Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Matteo Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Matteo Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - Inner City Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Lang Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Pearl Lang Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - Lewitzky Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Bella Lewitzky Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - Limon Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Jose Limon Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - Murray Louis Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Murray Louis Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - Lubovitch Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - M. Monk Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Nagrin Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Nagrin Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - Newman Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - G. Newman Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - Nikolais Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Nikolais Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Perez Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Rudy Perez Dance Theater Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - Pomare Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Pomare Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - RDT Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - RDT Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - Don Redlich Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - Don Redlich Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Rod Rogers Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Paul Sanasardo Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Paul Sanasardo Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - S. Shearer Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Sybil Shearer Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - Anna Sokolow Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Paul Taylor Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Paul Taylor Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - Twyla Tharp Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Twyla Tharp Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - Dan Wagoner Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Yuriko Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Yuriko Dance Co. Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 44)
  - Jacob's Pillow (Box 44)
  - Non-Proscenium, Spring Festival, May 1971 (Box 44)
  - Spring Dance Festival, 1971 (Box 44)
  - Spring Fling Clips, 1971 (Box 44)
  - General Info, Spring, 1971 (Box 44)
  - Spring Fling Correspondence (Box 44)
  - Rudy Perez (Box 44)
  - Theatre Workshop, Boston (Box 44)
  - Spring Fling Releases, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - Spring Fling General Information, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - New Generation, City Center (Box 44)
  - Spring Festival Permits, 1972 (Box 44)
  - Spring Festival, 1972 (Box 44)
  - Trisha Brown, Spring Fling (Box 44)
  - Spring Fling Phyllis Lamhut (Box 44)
  - Don Redlich, Spring Fling (Box 44)
  - Spring Fling Correspondence (Box 44)
  - Jamie Cunningham (Box 44)
  - Spring Festival, 1973 (Box 44)
  - Spring Festival Preliminary, 1973 (Box 44)
  - Spring Festival, 1976 (Box 44)
  - Spring Festival, 1976 (Box 44)
  - Spring Festival, 1975 (Box 45)
  - Spring Festival, 1974 (Box 45)
  - Spring Festival Company Sites, Schedules, Contacts, Etc., 1974 (Box 45)
  - Jacob's Pillow Companies, 1974 (Box 45)
  - Jacob's Pillow Contracts (Box 45)
  - J.P. Mass Choreographers Program, 1974 (Box 45)
  - Jacob's Pillow NEA Application (Box 45)
  - Jacob's Pillow Correspondence (Box 45)
  - Jacob's Pillow Financial (Box 45)
  - Jacob's Pillow Financial Information, 1973-1974 (Box 45)
  - Jacob's Pillow Mass Arts Council (Box 45)
  - Jacob's Pillow General Working (Box 45)
  - DTP (Box 45)
  - R70-33-39CN (Box 45)
  - Grant R60-33-69CN DTP Meetings, Grant Letter and Amendment, 1975-1976 (Box 45)
  - New DTP (Box 45)
  - DTP Directory, R70-33-37CN, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
  - DTP Directory, R60-33-140CN, 1976-1977 (Box 45)
  - DTP for D.C., 1974-1975 (Box 45)
  - DTP for D.C., 1975-1976 (Box 45)
  - DTP for D.C., 1976-1977 (Box 45)
  - DTP for D.C., 1977-1978 (Box 45)
  - Letter's of Inquiries (Box 45)
  - Grant Forms/Blank Cash Requests for DAP (Box 45)
  - Dance Assistance Project (Box 45)
  - DAP (Box 45)
  - Management and Administration Study, May 1976 (Box 45)
  - FY DTP Directory Master File, 1977 (Box 45)
  - State Art Council Correspondence, CRTP, 1974-1975 (Box 45)
  - Call Backs (Box 45)
  - DTP Meetings, Bills (Box 45)
  - DTP Meetings, Bills (Box 45)
  - DTP Meetings, Dance Companies, 1974-1975 (Box 46)
  - NEA Travel Forms (Box 46)
  - DTP Co's, Status of AIS Co. Application, Review for 1979-1980, 1978 (Box 46)
  - DMS/DC Applications for 1979-1980 Directory (Box 46)
  - Interested Applicants for 1979-1980 Directory, 1977 (Box 46)
  - Correspondence for Review Process for 1979-1980, 1978 (Box 46)
  - Mini-Panel Meeting (Review of Applicants), Feb. 13, 1978 (Box 46)
  - Mini-Panel Meeting II (Review of Applicants), June 5, 1978 (Box 46)
  - Letters of Acceptance and Rejection from NEA, 1979-1980 (Box 46)
  - Aman: The International Folk Ballet, Applied Fall, 1977 (Box 46)
  - Cartoon Opera, Applied Fall, 1977 (Box 46)
  - Frank Ashley Dance Company Co., Applied Fall, 1977 (Box 46)
  - Dances/Janet Soares, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - 5X2 Plus, Applied Fall, 1977, 1978 (Box 46)
  - Fusion Dance Company, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Paschal Guzman/Downtown Ballet. Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Hartford Chamber Ballet (Box 46)
  - I.D.E.A. Company, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - /inosiss, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Raymond Johnson Dance Company, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Claude Kipnis Mime Theater, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Ko-Thi Dance Company, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - R'Wanda Lewis Afro-American Dance Company, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Sophie Maslow Dance Co., Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Minnesota Dance Theatre, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Morca, Flamenco in Concert, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Mordine and Company, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Portland Dance Theatre, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Rod Rogers Dance Co., Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Solaris, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Edith Stephen Dance Collection, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Theatre Ballet of San Francisco, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Maruja Vargas and Compania del Oro, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Albert, Jill, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Baum, Maude, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Bordat, Nicole, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Salaam, Abdel (Bowser, Milton), Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Bromberg, Ellen, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Brown, Bradeline Shay, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Burton, Sandra Lynette, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Caplan, Roberta, Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Carson, Beatrice, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Claudia Chapline, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Chizik, Tedrian, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Clark, Karen, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Cook, Beverly, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Cowles, Diana Dinsmore, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Cristofori, Marilyn, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Ficken, Dennis Joseph, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Fossner, Ann Morris, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Franklin-White Peter, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Friede, Lynn, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Galloway, Lisa, Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Greene, Leslie, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Haskell, Phyllis Anne, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Constance Valis Hill, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Suzanne Hunter, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Hyatt, Janyce Johnson, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Jay, Danielle, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Kaemmerlen, Cathy J., Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Kindon, Ann, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Lane, Susan, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - R'Wanda Lewis, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Maloney, Julie, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Sophie Maslow, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - McColl, Sharon Lee, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Neri, Camilla, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Osserman, Wendy, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Packman, Jeri, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Partridge, Martha Ann, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Phillips, Dana, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Reynolds, Pearl, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Reynolds, Pearl, Applied Fall 1977 (Box 46)
  - Alvin Ailey City Center Dance Theatre, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Acme Dance Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Mary Anthony Dance Theatre, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Atlanta Ballet Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Ballet Repertory Company, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Ballet West, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Boston Ballet, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Chicago Contemporary Dance Theatre, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - The Cincinnati Ballet Company, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Ze'eva Cohen Solo Dance Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Dances We Dance, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Dance Theatre Of Harlem, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Eglevsky, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - George Faison Universal Dance Experience, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Viola Farber Dance Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - The First Chamber Dance Co. of N.Y., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Mimi Gerrard Dance Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Lotte Goslar's Pantomime Circus, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Martha Graham Dance Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Grand Union (Rio Grande Union), 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Jose Greco, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Nancy Hauser Dance Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Erick Hawkins Dance Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Houston Ballet Dance Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Inner City, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Joffrey II, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Elizabeth Keen Dance Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Cliff Kevter Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Kipnis Mime Theatre, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Phyllis Lamhut Dance Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Bella Lewitsky Dance Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Jose Limon Dance Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Murray Louis, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Burch Mann's Americana Dance Theatre, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Matteo and Indo-American Dance Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Minnesota Dance Theatre, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Meredith Monk, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Nagrin: Workgroup, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - National Ballet, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Nikolais, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - North Carolina Dance Theatre, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Margolit Oved, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Pennsylvania Ballet, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Poetry-in-Dance, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Eleo Pomare Dance Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Don Redlich, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Ririe-Woodbury, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Luis Rivera Spanish Dance, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Rod Rogers, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - San Francisco Ballet, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Paul Sanasardo, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - The Solomon's Co., 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Paul Taylor, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Tharp, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Theatre Flamenco of San Francisco, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Traditional Jazz, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Utah Repertory Dance Theatre, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Dan Wagoner, 1973-1974 (Box 47)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company Publicity Photographs, 1967 (Box 47)
  - Fees and Commissions (Box 47)
  - Duplicate CD, Apr. 1, 1980-Jan. 24, 1983 (Box 47)
  - Assorted Financial Tax Etc., 1983 (Box 47)
  - Paid FY, 1982-1983 (Box 47)
  - FY:CR Journal And ADP Transmittals, 1982-1983 (Box 47)
  - CRMI CR Journal, pre fy, 1982-1983 (Box 47)
  - CRMI CR Journal, pre fy, 1982-1983 (Box 47)
  - TBW (CRMI), Feb. 28, 1982 (Box 48)
  - CRMI, Assorted Financial, Tax Etc, 1984 (Box 48)
  - Final, Income Tax Return (Box 48)
  - TBW, CRMI, Dec. 31, 1981 (Box 48)
  - Disability (Box 48)
  - WRS, New York State, CRMI (Box 48)
  - Workmen's Comp (Box 48)
  - NY Unemployment /insurance Records, CRMI (Box 48)
  - Pending CRMI Corp Taxes (Box 48)
  - CRMI Corporate Taxes, 1983 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Corporate Tax Records, FYE, Mar. 31, 1982 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Corporate Tax Reports, FYE, Mar. 31, 1981 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Corporate Tax Reports, FYE, Mar. 31, 1980 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Corporate Tax Reports, FYE, Mar. 31, 1979 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Corporate Tax Reports, FYE, Mar. 31, 1978 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Corporate Tax Reports, FYE, Mar. 31, 1977 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Corporate Tax Reports, FYE, Mar. 31, 1976 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Corporate Tax Reports, FYE, Mar. 31, 1975 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Corporate Tax Reports, FYE, Mar. 31, 1974 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Corporate Tax Reports, FYE, Mar. 31, 1973 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Corporate Tax Reports, FYE, Mar. 31, 1972 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Corporate Tax Reports, FYE, Mar. 31, 1971 (Box 48)
  - Census, 1977 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Capital Stock (Box 48)
  - CRMI Deposits and Loans and Exchanges (Box 48)
  - CRMI Withholding, Spreadsheet of Tax Payments, PR Total by Person, Year End Rep (Box 48)
  - CRMI Corporate, Federal and State W/H Deposits, 1982-1983 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Unemployment Insurance, 1982 (Box 48)
  - FYE Notes and Paraphernalia, Mar. 31, 1981 (Box 48)
  - TBW, Mar. 21, 1981 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Notes FYE, Mar. 31, 1980 (Box 48)
  - 1099 Misc., 1976 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Payroll, 1976 (Box 48)
  - Payroll Taxes, 1976 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Payroll, 1975 (Box 48)
  - CRMI Unemployment /ins. History (Box 48)
  - Opera New England, 1974-1975 (Box 48)
  - Taxes, Tetley (Box 48)
  - Unemployment Notices, Glen Tetley, 1970 (Box 48)
  - General Ledger, 1972-1973 (Box 48)
  - General Ledger, 1971-1972 (Box 48)
  - General Ledger, 1977-1978 (Box 48)
  - General Ledger, 1974-1975 (Box 48)
  - General Ledger, 1975-1977 (Box 48)
  - General Ledger, Apr. 1967-Mar. 1968 (Box 48)
  - General Ledger, Apr. 1967-Mar. 1968 (Box 48)
  - General Ledger, Apr. 1966-Mar. 1967 (Box 49)
  - General Ledger, 1965-1966 (Box 49)
  - General Ledger, 1964 (Box 49)
  - General Ledger, Apr. 1970-Mar. 1971 (Box 49)
  - General Ledger, Cash Disbursements, Apr. 1969-Mar. 1970 (Box 49)
  - General Ledger, Apr. 1969-Mar. 1970 (Box 49)
  - General Ledger, Apr. 1968-Mar. 1969 (Box 49)
  - Pearl Lang, Tues. Feb. 2, Wed. Feb. 3, Sat. Mat. Feb. 6, 1970 (Box 49)
  - Paul Taylor, Mon, Feb. 8- Sat. Feb. 20, 1970-1971 (Box 49)